I like 'you', Mayama.
Why?
Because you're you.
That's not an answer.
Why do I like him so much?
I'm sure about one thing.
Mayama is my first real crush.
Why do you want to go out with me?
Because you're cool,
and kind, too.
I've never talked to you before.
How would you know I'm kind?
You should find someone else.
People always took one look at me,
and made assumptions.
Another confession?
[Year 1, Class 4]
How many is that now?
More than what it was in middle school?
Dunno. I haven't been keeping count.
- Dang.
- I'm jealous.
Hey, uh...
That's my seat.
Oh, my bad.
- Wanna be confessed to?
- I do.
Just wait, we're only in our first year.
Fair point. We'll have our opportunities.
At this point in time,
Mayama was just another classmate.
Yikes. Why couldn't I be in the same class...
Asamiya. I know you gotta dump them,
but be nice about it, yeah?
Sorry.
I took Sakaki's advice to heart.
Even though these girls
were making assumptions,
that was no reason to hurt their feelings.
I'm happy you feel that way.
But, I...
No, I understand. Thank you for listening.
I ignored my own discomfort,
and pretended to be nice.
- Let's go. Did you get it?
- Yup.
Awesome!
Asamiya! Come here.
I'm happy you feel that way.
But, I...
No, I understand. Thank you for listening.
The hell?
[Oh my god, he's so hot!]
[I want a shot with him, too!]
These comments are nasty.
Keep scrolling.
Damn, this is awful.
- Oh my god.
- There he is!
Hello! We saw the video.
Can we get a selfie together?
Why?
Huh?
To farm for likes on social media?
Don't use me as engagement bait.
My answer, is no.
No one thought about how I felt.
He's nothing like he is in the video.
He's just a shallow guy with the looks.
Yeah, seriously.
I was right to attend an all-boys school.
At least I could be at peace here.
Asamiya could totally pull off a dress.
If I posted a shot of that,
I'd get crazy likes.
- For sure.
- Hey!
- Let me get the likes!
- No way.
Seriously?
You don't even know me.
Hey, you should ask him about it.
I don't think Asamiya would appreciate that.
Dude, just go along with it.
Asamiya's feelings matter.
Uh, obviously we're not serious.
Still...
Whatever.
You're such a killjoy.
You put on the dress.
Yes, sir.
I can't believe Sakaki had to join
the Clean-Up Committee.
You two are waiting for Sakaki, right?
- Yeah.
- A teacher's chewing him out right now.
He was caught slacking,
so he had to stay behind.
I see.
Guess I'll go check on him.
That was my first conversation with Mayama.
Huh? The daily log...
What're you doing?
The daily log wasn't filled in yet.
The person on duty must've forgot.
It's not your job to fill it in.
But I found it blank.
So, you'll fill it in for them?
I'm sure they didn't forget on purpose.
Hopefully they won't get in trouble
for the small mistake.
Why'd you defend me the other day?
Huh?
The other dudes wanted me to crossdress.
Defending me wasn't doing you any favors.
Sure, but it's more important
to respect how you feel.
If they were egging me on like that,
I certainly wouldn't like it.
So I figured you wouldn't, either.
But I was just making assumptions.
Besides, I don't really care
if they come to dislike me.
Asamiya?
Ignore me.
Mayama's kind words mended by broken heart.
That conversation was the catalyst.
Great throw!
I would find myself looking at him from afar.
Hey, you dropped this.
Thanks.
At first, watching him was enough for me.
I needed the extra hand. Thank you.
You're welcome.
But as time passed...
Mayama.
I've got bread right here.
I'll take this one.
That'll be 120 yen.
I found Mayama's awkward kindness, endearing.
I wanted to get closer to him.
I wanted to touch him.
I wanted to hug him.
I wanted to make him all mine.
My admiration quickly changed
to something else entirely.
It didn't take long for me to realize
what I felt for him now, was "love".
If I conveyed these feelings of mine...
I knew they'd only trouble Mayama.
Yet, as fate would have it,
we were once again placed in the same class.
And with him sitting right in front of me...
[I like you.]
I couldn't hold myself back any longer.
Huh?
I thought I knew I'd only be troubling him.
There are better people out there for you.
Why did I say that?
This konjac jelly,
right by the entrance.
- Isn't it a bit much?
- Probably.
Let's take it out, and...
Time continued to pass,
as I remained unable to talk to Asamiya.
They won't expect it.
Yeah.
What about the exit?
Should we add more?
- No.
- Please, Komori?
We won't make it in time for the festival.
I still can't allow you
to stay on campus overnight.
And that's "Ms." Komori to you.
But, Komori...
Now what do we do?
Pull an all-nighter at somebody's place?
Mine's off limits.
My sister's studying for exams.
Same, my five siblings would bother us.
What about your place, Asamiya?
I remember it looking big,
not that I've ever been inside.
If none of your places work...
Pretty spacious, Mayama.
Yeah, this is perfect.
Great.
I didn't realize you lived so far, though.
Why'd you pick our school?
I had my reasons...
Here's some tea and snacks for you all.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
Of course. I'm happy to have
Hare's friends over.
Good luck on the festival prep.
- All right, let's get to it.
- Yeah.
I'm ready to work all night.
Same here.
- 'Sup!
- Dude.
Not the time.
Get to work.
Practice tomorrow.
- Aw, no practice?
- Not now.
We're here to crunch work.
Right.
I'm sweating.
This mask is stuffy.
"Need a guide"?
Dude, work.
I'm awake.
I'll go get us refreshments.
I'll join you.
I'm sorry we imposed.
Huh?
We all invited ourselves over, day of.
It's fine.
My room's never been that lively before.
I'm glad the space could help out.
You never change, do you?
I want our haunted house to be a success.
I've never worked in a group
with friends before.
In middle school...
my friends often made fun of me.
One time, they pulled this prank on me.
They said a girl in our class liked me.
That she wanted to confess.
So, during a summer festival,
I tried to politely turn her down.
But...
She didn't know what I was talking about.
Dude, obviously we were joking.
My friends all came to laugh at me.
She'd never confess to a guy like you.
Exactly.
I realized then it was all a joke.
Anyone would be hurt after that.
They used you for their own entertainment.
That's nothing a friend would do.
Asamiya. I'm happy you told me how you felt.
And I want to believe you, I really do.
But I can't help it. I'm still scared.
So, could you wait?
Just a bit longer, until I'm ready to answer?
I'll wait as long as you need me to.
And don't feel forced to answer, either.
We're back.
Ouch.
You okay?
Yeah, I just pricked myself.
I'll lick it clean.
You have to get that properly patched up.
[Bandage]
Sorry.
Huh?
I kept saying I liked you,
without even considering how you felt.
I made you feel horrible.
- No, I...
- Mayama.
You're always considerate
of my feelings, but I...
Asamiya.
You never made me feel bad.
It's just...
I don't know how I should treat you anymore.
- Just...
- Act normal, right?
I know.
I know that.
Still...
Let's do this.
Mayama?
Sorry.
Feel free to take a nap.
I'll be fine.
It's probably because I'm relieved.
I'm glad we finally made up.
You're too cute.
When you have a break during the festival,
do you want to check out
the other set-ups together?
Yeah. I want to eat crepes.
Sounds good.
Let's grab some takoyaki, too.
What else...
Mayama?
[Kitahara High Culture Festival]
Looking good.
- Thanks for helping.
- Sure.
Seriously, it looks great.
[Tenn Mayama (Esteemed brother)]
Hello?
Asamiya?
Good morning.
I'm sorry, Hare can't make it
to the festival today.
Huh?
I want to push through.
We all worked so hard on this.
Victory!
I think I'm ready
to give Asamiya my answer.
Let me stay like this.
I won't be able to stop myself.